brandscreen.com 2015-03-24

# Privacy - Brandscreen

## Effective: 1st August 2013

BRZX Pty Ltd (“Brandscreen”, “we” or “us”) recognizes the importance of trust and privacy.  
Brandscreen provides advertisers and publishers (“Business Partners”) access to a set of technologies and processes designed to display content and advertisements to consumers viewing website(s).

This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) applies to our web site at brandscreen.com (the “Site”) and our targeted advertising technology services (the “Technology”). In addition, where more detailed information is needed to explain our privacy practices, we post supplementary privacy notices to describe how particular services process Personally Identifiable Information (“PII” or “Personal Information”).

Brandscreen only collects and processes information for the purposes described in this Policy and/or the supplementary privacy notices for specific services. In addition to the descriptions in this Policy, such purposes include:

  * Providing our services, including the display of customized content and advertising;
  * Auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services;
  * Ensuring the technical functioning of our network;
  * Protecting the rights or property of Brandscreen or our users; and
  * Developing new services.

Brandscreen has been awarded TRUSTe’s Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with TRUSTe’s Web Privacy and TRUSTed Data program requirements including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your information. The TRUSTe programs cover only information that is collected through Brandscreen’s website, www.brandscreen.com, and network of third party desktop and mobile websites.

### Information we collect on the Site

#### Information you provide

When you sign up for a Brandscreen account or other Brandscreen service or promotion that requires registration, we ask you for Personal Information including but not limited to your name, email address and an account password. We may combine the information you submit under your account with information from other Brandscreen services or third parties in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our services.

#### Cookies

When you visit the Site, we send one or more cookies – a small file containing a string of characters – to your computer or other device that uniquely identifies your browser. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some Brandscreen features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service, including for storing user preferences, improving search results and ad selection, and tracking user trends.  
We use HTML 5 local storage objects (LSOs) to store content information and account preferences on our Site. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs.

#### Pixel Tags and Beacons

We also use pixel tags, sometimes known as web beacons or clear gifs, to assist us with our Site operations. Pixel tags inform us how visitors interact with our Site.

#### Third Party Technologies

We partner with third parties that use cookies, pixel tags and scripts on our Site. Some of these technologies are used to assist us with maintenance and performance of the Site. Others are used to assist us with managing our advertising on other websites you may visit. If you wish to not have information about your visit to this Site used to display ads that may be of interest to you, please [click here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). The use of these technologies by our partners and service providers is not covered by our Policy. We do not have access or control over these technologies and they do not collect any personal information you may submit to our Site.

#### Log information

When you access the Brandscreen Site, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

#### User communications

When you send email or other communications to Brandscreen, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.

#### Affiliated Brandscreen Services on other sites

We offer some of our services on or through other web sites. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to Brandscreen in order to deliver the service. We process such information under this Policy. The affiliated sites through which our services are offered may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies.

#### Referrals

We provide you the ability to enter your friend’s email address, inviting them to visit the Site. We use their email address, and the content of your message, in order to send him or her a one-time email. This information is not stored for any other purpose.  
Our Site also provides third-party Open ID services, such as Facebook Connect, that will allow you to share certain personal information with us, such as your name and email address. Open ID services give you the option to post information about your activities on our Site and to share with others within your network.

#### Applications

Brandscreen may make available third party applications (“Applications”) through its services. The information collected by Brandscreen when you enable another Application is processed under this Policy. Information collected by the Application provider is governed by their privacy policies.

#### Other sites

This Policy applies to the Brandscreen Site only. We do not exercise control over products or services, or links from within our various services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.

#### Choices for personal information

If we use Personal Information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use. If we propose to use Personal Information for any purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service privacy notices, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of Personal Information for those other purposes. We will not collect or use sensitive information for purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the supplementary service privacy notices, unless we have obtained your prior consent. You can decline to submit Personal Information to any of our services, in which case Brandscreen may not be able to provide those services to you.

#### Accessing and updating personal information

When you use Brandscreen services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your Personal Information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort. Some of our services have different procedures to access, correct or delete users’ personal information. We provide the details for these procedures in the specific privacy notices or FAQs for these services. Or, contact us via one of the methods listed below.

#### Data protection

Brandscreen processes Personal Information on our servers in Singapore and in other countries. In some cases, we process Personal Information on a server outside your own country. We may process Personal Information to provide our own services. In some cases, we may process Personal Information on behalf of and according to the instructions of a third party, such as our advertising partners.

#### Information sharing

Brandscreen only shares Personal Information with other companies or individuals outside of Brandscreen in the following limited circumstances:  
We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive Personal Information.  
We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing Personal Information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Brandscreen, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

If Brandscreen becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will ensure the confidentiality of any Personal Information involved in such transactions and provide notice before Personal Information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.  
Please contact us for any additional questions about the management or use of personal data.

### Information we collect through the Technology

Our Technology allows our Business Partners to collect information about the website(s) that you visit and the advertisements that you see while online and to display advertisements and content that may be relevant to your interests. Our Technology collects information about your interactions with third party desktop and mobile websites. You may encounter our Technology when Brandscreen or one of our Business Partners purchase online advertisements on a website that you visit or mobile application that you use; and/or when one of our Business Partners places one of our web beacons on its website or within its mobile application.

#### Information we collect

Brandscreen does not collect or use Personally Information using the Technology and prohibit Business Partners from collecting or using PII with the Technology. When you interact with a site where our Technology appears, we may receive non-Personally Identifiable Information (such as your IP address, browser language, or URL of the site you visited). For mobile services, we may also receive an identifier of your mobile device. We may combine the information our Technology collects directly with information from other third parties in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our services. This additional third party data may contain demographic or interest-based information.

#### Cookies

Brandscreen uses cookies in its advertising services to help Business Partners serve and manage ads across the web. We may set one or more cookies in your browser when you visit a website, including Brandscreen sites that use our advertising cookies, and view or click on an ad supported by our Technology.

#### Pixel Tags and Beacons

We also use pixel tags, sometimes known as web beacons or clear gifs, to assist us with our Technology. Pixel tags inform us when you have interacted with an advertisement and help us better understand the effectiveness of our services.

#### Log information

When you access our Technology, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

#### Opting Out

You may opt out of our use of the information we collect through our technologies for targeted advertising. To opt out of seeing advertisements and content that may be tailored to your interests by Brandscreen, please click here:

#### Information sharing

We may share the information we receive through our Technology with our Business Partners. We may share audience segments with third party service providers (e.g., cloud processing and storage) in order for those service providers to perform business functions for us or on our behalf. We may also disclose the information we receive if we believe that we have a legal obligation to do so, such as to comply with a subpoena or similar legal process, or in situations where we believe necessary to protect ourselves, our Business Partners or users to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or poses a risk of being, illegal or legally actionable activity. In addition, we may transfer all or some of the data, in connection with a corporate merger, acquisition, sale of assets, bankruptcy, or other change in corporate status.

#### Other sites

This Policy applies to our Technology only. Content delivered by our Technology may contain links to other websites. We do not exercise control over products or services, or links from within our various services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit Personal Information from you.

#### Information about children

We do not knowingly collect data about or target children under the age of thirteen (13). Children under the age of 13 may be placed into one of our general audience segments, based on the web activity of the computer/browser they are using. We are unable to prevent this as we do not collect Personal Information and we don’t collect information with the intent of identifying users as being under the age of 13.

#### Information security

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.  
We restrict access to Personal Information to Brandscreen employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

#### Data integrity

Brandscreen processes Personal Information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the Personal Information needed to provide or improve our services or as otherwise permitted under this Policy. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the Personal Information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their Personal Information whenever necessary.

#### Data Retention

We will retain the information we collect through our Technology for up to 180 days. After 180 days, some of the information we have (e.g., anonymous logs) may be aggregated for statistical purposes and stored indefinitely, and the rest of the information is destroyed.  
The information that we obtain through the Site is retained for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

#### Enforcement

Brandscreen regularly reviews its compliance with this Policy. We encourage interested persons to raise any concerns using the contact information provided and we will investigate and attempt to resolve any complaints and disputes regarding use and disclosure of information.  
When we receive formal written complaints, it is Brandscreen’s policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between Brandscreen and an individual.

#### Contact Information

If you have any questions or concerns about this Policy, please feel free to contact us any time through this web site or at privacy@brandscreen.com.

#### Privacy Officer

BRZX Pty Ltd, Level 2 30 Alfred Street Milsons Point NSW 2061  
If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact TRUSTe.

#### Changes to this Policy

Please note that this Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Policy changes) prior to the changes taking effect. Each version of this Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date, and we will also keep prior versions of this Policy in an archive for your review.
